

CONTACT DETAILS

+27 (0)67 719 3590 moyo.khanyi@gmail.com

KHANYISILE MOYO

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a highly organised individual with great communication and interpersonal skills, and have one and a half years' experience working as an administrator and tutoring combined. I have strong typing and data entry skills, and enjoy working independently as well as in a team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Office Manager Dali Powell Studios | Jan 2020 - September 2020

- Coordinated schedules, appointments and bookings
- Ensured filing systems were maintained and current
- Monitored and recorded daily expenses
- Ordered and maintain office supplies

Online English Tutor

Independent | Mar 2019 - August 2020

- Create lesson planning
- Provide feedback
- Assess student performance

Assistant Administrator The Metropolitan College | Jan 2018 - Dec 2018

- Maintained calendars and schedules
- Prepared and distributed minutes of meetings
- Answered, screened and directed incoming calls
- Managed travel arrangements

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

AFDA

BA Motion Picture Medium | 2016 - 2018

• Writing, editing and producing

AFDA

BA (Hons.) Motion Picture Medium | 2019 - 2019

Producing

SKILLS

Microsoft Office Zoom/Skype/Google

Hangout

Asana Adobe Premier Pro

Canva Adobe Illustrator